Guide to the Vassar College Class Records, 1865-2021
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Vassar College Class Records
1865-2021
Vassar College
56.6 cubic feet (174 boxes, 7 volumes)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Materials from the various classes of Vassar College, mostly concerning graduation, reunion, and alumnae/i activities.
Scope and Content Note
Materials from the various graduating classes, including minutes and account books from class organizations, alumnae questionnaires, programs, bulletins, invitations, songbooks, reunion materials, clippings and articles on class members, and some notes and letters.
The records of the Class of 1889 include one volume of biographical sketches prepared for the 50th reunion, containing information on family, career, travels, and reminiscences of college years; one biography from a physician includes her reactions to studying with Carl Jung in the 1920s.
The records of the Class of 1914 inlclude 3 scrapbooks containing photographs, clippings, programs, and captions concerning the women in the class and their subsequent lives, circa 1910-1964.
The collection contains no records for the classes of 1945-4 or 1954.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into series for each graduating class, beginning in 1867 and ending 1979. Records of the classes of 1980 and later are grouped together. The last series in the collection consists of copper printing plates and printing blocks of class trees and class bookplates from 1868 to 1923. Materials within each series are arranged alphabetically by title.
Access
This collection is open for research according to the regulations of the Vassar College Archives and Special Collections Library without any additional restrictions.
Related Materials
Vassar College Realia Collection
Subject Headings
Organizations:
Vassar College. Class of 1889; Vassar College. Class of 1898; Vassar College. Class of 1912; Vassar College. Class of 1914; Vassar College. Class of 1951; Vassar College--Alumni and alumnae; Vassar College--Students; Vassar College--Songs
Subjects:
Women's colleges--New York (State)--Poughkeepsie; Women--Societies and clubs; Women college students--New York (State)--Poughkeepsie
Document Types:
Correspondence; Photographs; Printed ephemera; Printing blocks (printing surfaces); Printing plates; Realia; Scrapbooks
VCL Categories:
Vassar College Students and Alumnae/i
Encoding Information
Encoded by Emma Gronbeck, March 2025.
Acquisition Information
Gift of various classes and individuals, as well as transfers from the Alumnae/i Association of Vassar College.
Accessions: A2006-022, A2006-039, A2007-052, A2008-001, A2009-016, A2009-019, A2009-030, A2009-046, A2010-003, A2010-004, A2010-036, A2011-004, A2011-005, A2011-023, A2011-024, A2011-033, A2011-034, A2012-022, A2013-005, A2014-013, A2014-028, A2014-050, A2015-003, A2016-014, A2019-021, A2021-023, and A2024-009.
Series List
  1867 — 1868 — 1869—
  1870 — 1871 — 1872 — 1873 — 1874 — 1875 — 1876 — 1877 — 1878 — 1879—
  1880 — 1881 — 1882 — 1883 — 1884 — 1885 — 1886 — 1887 — 1888 — 1889—
  1890 — 1891 — 1892 — 1893 — 1894 — 1895 — 1896 — 1897 — 1898 — 1899—
  1900 — 1901 — 1902 — 1903 — 1904 — 1905 — 1906 — 1907 — 1908 — 1909—
  1910 — 1911 — 1912 — 1913 — 1914 — 1915 — 1916 — 1917 — 1918 — 1919—
  1920 — 1921 — 1922 — 1923 — 1924 — 1925 — 1926 — 1927 — 1928 — 1929—
  1930 — 1931 — 1932 — 1933 — 1934 — 1935 — 1936 — 1937 — 1938 — 1939—
  1940 — 1941 — 1942 — 1943 — 1944 — 1945-4 — 1945 — 1946 — 1947 — 1948 — 1949—
  1950 — 1951 — 1952 — 1953 — 1954 — 1955 — 1956 — 1957 — 1958 — 1959—
  1960 — 1961 — 1962 — 1963 — 1964 — 1965 — 1966 — 1967 — 1968 — 1969—
  1970 — 1971 — 1972 — 1973 — 1974 — 1975 — 1976 — 1977 — 1978 — 1979—
  1980-2007 — Printing Plates —
Container List
- Class of 1867, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - 2 invoices and 2 receipts made out to Caroline E. Slade for board, tuition and extra changes at VC, 1865-1866 (Box 1)
  - 2 letters written to the Slade sisters at VC, 1865-1866 (Box 1)
  - Christmas card from Harriette Bishop, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1867 1st Founder's Day Program, undated (Box 1)
  - Letter written by Frances Elizabeth Brown to Caroline E. Slade during summer vacation, 1865-1866 (Box 1)
  - Photographs - Children of Alice (Parter) Dungen, 1866-1867 (Box 1)
  - Photographs - Children of Maria (Dickinson) McGraw, undated (Box 1)
  - Photographs: children of McMaher, Elizabeth (Geiger) (VC 1867), undated (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Shoe, wedding veil, orange blossom wreath. Worn by Emma Amelia (Culver) Kimball, 1865-1867 (Box 1)
  - Valentine sent to Abigail L. Slade, 1866 (Box 1)
- Class of 1868, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - "1868 class papers (stationary),", undated (Box 1)
  - "Class History 1868-1918,", undated (Box 1)
  - "History of the Class of 1868 of Vassar College 1885-1893,", undated (Box 1)
  - Article - "Mary Cornell (VC 1868) Will be 84 on Saturday,", undated (Box 1)
  - Chronicle, Third reunion of the class of 1868, 1885 Jun (Box 1)
  - Class day program, 1868 (Box 1)
  - Info on "L. Augusta and Anna Corning Library Endowment Fund,", undated (Box 1)
  - Invitation to class day/commencement, 1868 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous letters, undated (Box 1)
  - Newspaper clippings - "Aspirations" by Jones, Ella (VC 1868), undated (Box 1)
  - Photograph - children of Marie (Stagg) Fulton (VC 1868), undated (Box 1)
  - Photographs of children of Clara (Glone) Gunn (VC 1868), undated (Box 1)
  - Photographs of Mary Garrison Smith 1868 and her mother, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1869, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Book - Mary S. Coustant 1869 "Album of the Heart,", undated (Box 1)
  - Class Day Book, 1869 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence from Sarah l. Stilson (VC 1869), undated (Box 1)
  - Photographs - Children of alumnae, undated (Box 1)
  - Records of various reunions for the class of 1869, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1870, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Article - "A Who's Who of the College's Fifty-Year Class,", undated (Box 1)
  - Booklet - "The Library of Ms. Mary Harriott Norris, to be sold at auction,", undated (Box 1)
  - Class day exercise leaflet (shaped like VC logo), undated (Box 1)
  - Class exercises at 20th reunion, 1890 Jun 10; [3 copies] (Box 1)
  - Correspondence to/from Mary A. Mineah, undated (Box 1)
  - Correspondence/ephemera - "Miss Mineah's notes on E. A. Abbey,", undated (Box 1)
  - Essay by Ellen H. Richards (VC 1870) - "The Relation of College Women to Progress in Domestic Science,", undated (Box 1)
  - Essay by Mary (Parker) Woodwort (VC 1870) - "The Science of Flirting,", undated; [3 copies] (Box 1)
  - Lab report by Ellen Henrietta (Swallow) Richards (VC 1870), undated (Box 1)
  - Leaflet on class memorial fund, undated (Box 1)
  - Leaflet on Elizabeth Drinker Storer Memorial Fund, undated (Box 1)
  - Lyrics to "Farewell Song - Class of 1870 to class of 1869,", undated (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous class correspondence, undated (Box 1)
  - Photograph - children of Amanda (Woodo) Ewing (VC 1870), undated (Box 1)
  - Records/correspondence to Elizabeth Coffin (VC 1870), undated (Box 1)
  - Tree day ceremony records, undated (Box 1)
  - VC Thanksgiving Dinner menu, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1871, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Class record book, undated (Box 1)
  - Leaflet on the Fannie Lovell Colman fund, undated (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous photographs of campus, undated (Box 1)
  - Notebook of Euphemia Ward Hopper (VC 1871), undated (Box 1)
  - Notice to class of 1871 on 50th reunion, 1921 (Box 1)
  - Reunion material of Euphemia Ward Hopper (VC 1871), undated (Box 1)
  - Tuition checks for Emma Cornell (VC 1871), undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1872, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Article - "Letters from a young mother reveal life in Victorian Oakland,", undated (Box 1)
  - Class ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Photograph - children of Abby Fanwell Ferry (VC 1872), undated (Box 1)
  - Photograph (Gift of Nancy Corson, VC 1872), 1889 Jan 2 (Box 1)
- Class of 1873, [0.6 cubic feet (2 boxes)]
  - Announcements related to alumnae of 1873 (deaths, etc.), undated (Box 1)
  - Class day materials, undated (Box 1)
  - Class notes from VQ, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1873 badge (fabric), undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1873 class record book, undated; [2 books] (Box 2)
  - Class of 1873 memory book plate, undated (Box 2)
  - Letter to classmate from Cornelia Fitch, undated (Box 1)
  - Letters collected by Myra Clark, undated (Box 1)
  - Photograph - child of "Minnie" Raymond Richardson (VC 1873), undated (Box 1)
  - Photograph - child of Julia Chapin Wilbor (VC 1873), undated (Box 1)
  - Photograph - child of Lillian Thomas Elder (VC 1873), undated (Box 1)
  - Photograph - child of Myra Clark (VC 1873), undated (Box 1)
  - Photograph - daughter of Marnie Brayton (Borden) (VC 1873), undated (Box 1)
  - Record of 1873 reunion, 1913 (Box 1)
- Class of 1874, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Booklet - "The Rhyme of the Birthday Trees,", undated (Box 1)
  - Class day materials, undated (Box 1)
  - Class ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Newspaper article - "Wed Early, 1874 Urges Girl Grads,", undated (Box 1)
  - Notices on Florence M. Cushing Fund (est. 1927), undated (Box 1)
  - Photograph - Hattie Ohlen Shephard (VC 1874), undated (Box 1)
  - Photograph - McMillan Allen (VC 1874), undated (Box 1)
  - Vassar College 1874 Class Book, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1875, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Class day exercises booklet, undated (Box 1)
  - Correspondence to Comstock, Ida B. Cummings (VC 1875), undated (Box 1)
  - Newspaper - "Vassar 1875 goes back,", undated (Box 1)
  - Photograph - Josephine (Jewell) Dodge (VC 1875), undated (Box 1)
  - Photographs of 1875 alumnae, undated (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1876, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Class day exercises booklet/materials, undated; [4 booklets] (Box 1)
  - Class ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Materials collected by Mary L. "Minnie" Adams, undated (Box 1)
  - Photographs of alumnae, undated (Box 1)
  - Photographs of Katherine Cochran (Hale) 1876 and her husband and their wedding invitation, undated (Box 1)
  - Program - "Guy Mannering,", undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1877, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - "Herman and Dorothea" by Goethe - belonged to a "prep" student at VC, 1871-1872 (Box 1)
  - Baccalaureate Sermon and Class Day Exercises booklet, undated (Box 1)
  - Correspondence to Emma (Sutra) Merritt (VC 1877), 1876-1877 (Box 1)
  - Photographs of Mary Thaw Thompson (VC 1877), undated (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1878, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Baccalaureate service booklet, undated (Box 1)
  - Booklet - "Reunion Poem,", 1903 (Box 1)
  - Booklet - "The Past, related by Miss Rollins,", undated (Box 1)
  - Class history 50th reunion letter, 1903 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1878 50th anniversary book, 1928 (Box 1)
  - Class reunion materials, undated (Box 1)
  - "Godey's Lady's Book,", 1878 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous class correspondence, undated (Box 1)
  - "Pink and grey chiffon worn by Ella McCaleb at her 50th reunion in 1928 Also worn by Helen Daves Brown 1878 at her 56th reunion in 1934,", (g. Florence McCaleb, VC 1969) (Box 1)
  - "Poems, Prophecy, and Histories of the class of 1878,", undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - La Societe Erckman-Chatrian certificate + program 1878 material, undated (Box 1)
  - "Vassariana 1874-1878,", undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1879, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Baccalaureate service booklet, undated (Box 1)
  - Compass tools, Blandina Cuddeback (Prep 1874-5, 1875-6), undated (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous class correspondence, undated (Box 1)
  - Obituary of Emily Folger (VC 1879), undated (Box 1)
  - Purse in which 1879 presented its class gift at its 20th reunion, 1899 (Box 1)
- Class of 1880, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Baccalaureate Sermon, Commencement Program, and memorabilia, 1880 (Box 1)
  - Desk calendar, 1880 (Box 1)
  - Handkerchief belonging to Caroline B. Dow (VC 1880), undated; (g. Margaret (Elder) Dow, VC 1904) (Box 1)
  - Invitations, seating cards, 1880 (Box 1)
  - Photograph - children of Mary Morris Pratt, undated (Box 1)
  - Photographs - Children of alumnae, undated (Box 1)
  - Photographs - Mary Morris, Georgia Coles, Jane Cushing, Lydia Psau and Mary Morris memorabilia, undated (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1881, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Class Day Book, 1881; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1881 - drafts of class letter, undated (Box 1)
  - "Class of 1881 - Poems, Prophecy, and Histories,", undated (Box 1)
  - Class reunion materials, undated (Box 1)
  - Baccalaureate service booklet, undated (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous ephemera, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1882, [0.6 cubic feet (2 boxes)]
  - Book - class of 1882 history, undated; [2 books] (Box 2)
  - Class day exercises booklet, undated (Box 1)
  - Class Day pamphlets 1882 and "History, Poem + Prophecy," (Box 1)
  - Class financial records, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1882 50th anniversary photographs, 1932 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1882 bookplates, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1882 class record book, undated (Box 1)
  - Mary Easton Conable 1882 papers - correspondence, records, etc., undated (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Vassar Council meeting record, 1932 Apr 23 (Box 1)
  - Young, Fanny (Taylor) - History of the class of 1882... 3rd reunion, 1895 Jun 11 (Box 2)
- Class of 1883, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - "'85's Trig. Ceremonies,", 1883; (g. Mary F. Pass, VC 1883) (Box 1)
  - 25th anniversary of 1883 pamphlet, 1908 (Box 1)
  - Baccalaureate Sermon, class day exercises, 1883 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1883 bookplates and stationary seal, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1883 fan (signed) - Class of 1883 E.G.M., undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1883 Reunion Address, undated (Box 1)
  - "History, Poem, and Propechy,", 1879; (g. Mary F. Pass, VC 1883) (Box 1)
  - Mary F. Pass (VC 1883) collection: invitations, seating cards, thank-you notes, undated (Box 1)
  - Mary Press Fearrington Papers (VC 1883), undated; (g. Emiline Thorne Brawley, VC 1936) (Box 1)
  - Photograph - Children of Ida Cushing Underwood (VC 1883), undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1884, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Baccalaureate service booklet, 1884 (Box 1)
  - Booklet - "A Genealogy and some other facts about the Class of 1884,", undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1884 bookplates, undated (Box 1)
  - Photographs - Children of alumnae, undated (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1885, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Baccalaureate service booklet, undated (Box 1)
  - Bertrice Shattuck Fulton - includes photographs of her daughter, Ruth (Fulton) Benedict (VC 1909), undated (Box 1)
  - Booklet - "Dr. Faustus 1887's Trig. Ceremony,", 1885 Feb 14 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1885 bookplates, undated (Box 1)
  - Photographs - Children of alumnae, undated (Box 1)
  - Vassar stationary, 1885 (Box 1)
- Class of 1886, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - 25th anniversary book Class of 1886, undated (Box 1)
  - "Back to Vassar" book, 1886-1911; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class day book 1886 (Box 1)
  - Class day book 1886 - Baccalaureate Sermon and class day exercises (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Scarf banner 1886, undated (Box 1)
  - Watercolor - portrait of by R. Wilkinson, 1895 (Box 1)
- Class of 1887, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Class of 1887 bookplates, undated (Box 1)
  - Memorabilia of Ida Frank Guttman (VC 1887) - travel photographs, red cross certificate, undated (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Silk flag class of 1887, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1888, [1 cubic foot (3 boxes)]
  - Book of verse, undated (Box 3)
  - Class correspondence, 1921-1929 (Box 2)
  - Class correspondence, 1930-1937 (Box 2)
  - Class correspondence, 1938 (Box 2)
  - Class day book 1888 (Box 3)
  - Class of 1888 50th reunion material, 1938 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1888 correspondence, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1888 photographs, undated (Box 3)
  - Class of 1888 statistics and children and Express list, undated (Box 3)
  - Class of 1888 biographical questions, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1888 fund, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1888 Letters to Adelaide Underhill, undated (Box 2)
  - Class representative's reports, undated (Box 1)
  - Class secretary's bulletin, undated (Box 1)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 1)
  - Correspondence about the "C.L." class letters, undated (Box 2)
  - File of secretary's annual bulletin, undated (Box 1)
  - Girls' school catalogue, undated (Box 3)
  - Last Wills of 1888, undated (Box 2)
  - Ledger to which Martha Reynolds attached to memorabilia from European tour, undated (Box 3)
  - Martha Hyer Millard + Harris Smith Reynolds wedding certificate photo and article, undated (Box 3)
  - Martha Reynolds memorabilia, undated (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous memorabilia, undated (Box 3)
  - Miss Ransom and Miss Bridges' School for Girls - Miss Adelaide Underhill, 1931-1932 (Box 3)
  - Miss Ransom and Miss Bridges' School for Girls catalogue, 1924 (Box 3)
  - nonsense rhymes attributed to Gelett Burgess, undated (Box 3)
  - Postcards received by Adelaide Underwood (VC 1888) and bookplates in memory of her, undated (Box 3)
  - Secretary's bulletin, 1935-1936 (Box 1)
- Class of 1889, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Biographical Sketches of members of the class of 1889, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1889 class letters, 1911 Sep 10 - 1913 Jun 24 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1889 class letters, 1913 Aug 19 - 1914 Jan 23 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1889 class letters, 1914 Mar 4 - 1915 Aug 29 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1889 envelope, undated (Box 1)
  - Folder with bookplates, Caroline Weeks notes on relaxation, class day book, photographs Annie Nettleton Bourne, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1890, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - 8 senior photographs and rock section slides, undated (Box 1)
  - Biographical notice on Katherine Carpenter Carr (VC 1890), undated (Box 1)
  - Booklet - "In Oblivionem Trigonometri,", 1888 Feb 18 (Box 1)
  - Class day book, undated (Box 1)
  - Horn of 1890, undated (Box 1)
  - Letter from Cora L. Scofield to Miss Thorton, undated (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper articles, undated (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Program for The Musical Arts Association, undated (Box 1)
  - Report of the second reunion of the Class of 1890, 1895 Jun 11 (Box 1)
  - VC 25th anniversary book, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1891, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Class book and class songs, 1891 (Box 1)
  - Class day book, 1891 Jun 9 (Box 1)
- Class of 1892, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Class day book, 1892 Jun 7 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1892 envelope, undated (Box 1)
  - Edith Banfield sketchbook, undated (Box 1)
  - Letters from 1892, undated (Box 1)
  - Photographs of Helen King 1892 and Lucia Wood 1892, undated (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Vassarion, 1892 (Box 1)
- Class of 1893, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Class of 1893's progress - scroll 1, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1893's progress - scroll 2, undated (Box 1)
  - Elisabeth B. Cutting memorabilia - metals, honors society membership, sash, undated (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Trig. ceremony scroll, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1894, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - 50th anniversary address, biographical data + more, 1944 (Box 1)
  - Class day book, 1894 Jun 12 (Box 1)
  - Class day book + program, 1894 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1894 class bulletin, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1894 metal plaque, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1894 trig. ceremonies, undated (Box 1)
  - Commencement program, 1894 Jun 13; [3 copies] (Box 1)
  - Mabel Hastings memorabilia, invitations, poems, valentines, undated (Box 1)
  - Photographs - Children of alumnae, undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "A Problem in Adverse Sailing,", undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1895, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - American College of Musicians certificate, undated (Box 1)
  - Class day book + trig ceremonies program, 1895 (Box 1)
  - Class day program, 1895 (Box 1)
  - Dutchess County Historical Society yearbook, 1941 (Box 1)
  - "North Iowa Times, issue 46,", undated (Box 1)
  - Photograph - Vassar alumnae, undated (Box 1)
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - "Speeches from 1895's Trig Ceremonies,", undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1896, [0.6 cubic feet (2 boxes)]
  - Bookplates class of 1896, undated (Box 1)
  - Class day book, 1896 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1896 "Puzzled Student" poster, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1896 Bargain Day poster, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1896 class record book, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1896 clippings, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1896 correspondence, A.M. Whaley to C.L. Fish from Alaska + photographs, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1896 in 1898 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1896 programs, catalogue, register, trig ceremonies, reunions, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1896 Remainder of programs, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1896 reunion, 1924; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - Class of 1896 reunion, 1928; [3 copies] (Box 2)
  - Class of 1896 reunion, 1933 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous clippings + programs, undated (Box 2)
  - Photographs - class of 1896, undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "A Problem in Adverse Sailing,", undated (Box 2)
  - Reunion reports, undated (Box 1)
  - Senior sale poster, undated (Box 1)
  - Treasurer's report, 1892-1946 (Box 2)
- Class of 1897, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Class day book, undated (Box 1)
  - Class day book, programs of 5th, 10th reunion, "bulletins,", undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1897 bookplate, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1897 bookplates and memorabilia, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1897 correspondence, undated (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous materials, undated; [2 envelopes] (Box 1)
  - Photographs and 2 tokens, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1898, [3.6 cubic feet (12 boxes)]
  - Annual bulletins of the class of 1898, undated (Box 2)
  - Class bibliography folder, undated (Box 11)
  - Class book, 1898 Jun 7; [3 copies] (Box 2)
  - Class of 1898 - 25th reunion information, 1923 (Box 12)
  - Class of 1898 - 40th reunion information, 1938 (Box 12)
  - Class of 1898 - 50th reunion information, 1948 (Box 12)
  - Class of 1898 - 75th reunion information, 1973 (Box 12)
  - Class of 1898 authors, undated (Box 11)
  - Class of 1898 binder with letters from graduate and non-graduate members, family, and the deceased, undated (Box 3)
  - Class of 1898 bulletin, 1952; [2 copies] (Box 9)
  - Class of 1898 bulletin - 50th Anniversary, 1949 (Box 12)
  - Class of 1898 Bulletin No. 23, 1936 Jul (Box 12)
  - Class of 1898 bulletin submission request, undated (Box 7)
  - Class of 1898 bulletin supplement, 1952 (Box 4)
  - Class of 1898 class songs mailed to Fanny Borden, undated (Box 11)
  - Class of 1898 gifts to VCL, undated (Box 11)
  - Class of 1898 Library fund, undated (Box 2)
  - Class of 1898 record book no. 1, undated (Box 8)
  - Class of 1898 record book no. 2, undated (Box 6)
  - Class of 1898 record book no. 3, undated (Box 5)
  - Class of 1898 reunion notes - 49th anniversary, 1947 May (Box 9)
  - Class of 1898 reunion schedule, undated (Box 7)
  - Class of 1898: letters, undated (Box 1)
  - Class reports, letters, vouchers, 1929-1934 (Box 4)
  - Class reports, vouchers, and receipts, 1924-1929 (Box 4)
  - Class songs, 1898; [2 copies] (Box 7)
  - Class vouchers, 1934-1938 (Box 4)
  - Class vouchers, 1938-1947 (Box 4)
  - Class vouchers, 1948-1950 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence from Fanny Borden to Mrs. Walter V. Cotchett, undated (Box 11)
  - Donation cards, undated (Box 3)
  - "Extras for PVV,", undated (Box 11)
  - Informal reunion cards, undated (Box 3)
  - Letters to Fanny Borden from the Class of 1898, undated; [8 folders] (Box 10)
  - Library fund information, undated (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence to Fanny Borden, undated (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box 4)